## Kirby Armstrong

#79 Guanapo Street,

#### ARIMA

Email:-kirbykiara@yahoo.com Telephone: - (868) 377-5855

Dear Sir/Madam,

## **Re: Career Opportunity:**

The accompanying resume is presented for your review and consideration for the position of General Services.

My ability to learn quickly, easily grasp complex concepts, and assume increased levels of responsibility, and complete assignments independently or as part of a team with a high level of performance. In addition, I am a diplomatic, eager and experienced professional, and have held positions of leadership and responsibility centered on, overseeing day-to-day operations in areas of human resource functions, generating and retaining new business, sales, customer service, policy changes and staff supervision.

With the firm emphasis I place on accountability and hard work, I feel I can be a strong asset to your organization. I welcome the opportunity to further discuss my candidacy and would love the opportunity to interview and learn more about your organization. Thank you for your time and consideration.

Yours Truly, KIRBY ARMSTRONG (MS.)

## Kirby Christiana Armstrong

# 79 Guanapo Street, Arima Email:-<u>kirbykiara@yahoo.com</u> Telephone: - (868) 377-5855

### **CAREER OBJECTIVES**

To continue to develop into a unique individual; to work within a dynamic challenging organization; whereby my acquired skills can be effectively utilized in order to ensure the successful realization of the company's goal.

#### **EDUCATION**

St. Augustine Senior Comprehensive School

Cor.Warren and Gordon Streets

**ST.AUGUSTINE (2001-2003)** 

Five Rivers Junior Secondary

Five Rivers

AROUCA (1999-2001)

Arima Girls Roman Catholic School

ARIMA (1993-1999)

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: - 06th December, 1985

Nationality: - Trinidadian Marital Status: - Single

# ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS CARIBBEAN EXAMINATION COUNCIL-CXC

English A- II
Office Administration- II
Integrated Science III
Social Studies III

Mathematics Awaiting Certificate

#### OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

2014 BACHELORS OF ADMINSTRATION IN HUMAN RESOURCE

**MANAGEMENT** 

U.S.C.

University of the Southern Caribbean

Maracas St. Joseph September-Present

2013 CERTIFICATE IN HUMAN RESOURCE MANAGEMENT

**SBCS** 

School of Business & Computer Sciences Ltd.

Champs Fleurs

September-November

2013 CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION PATIENT CARE ASSISTANT

**YTEPP** 

Youth Training Employment Partnership Programme

Arima

February - August

2012 CERTIFICATE IN CHILD CARE ATTENDANT

**YTEPP** 

Youth Training Employment Partnership Programme

Arima

July - December

2012 CERTIFICATE OF ACHEIVEMENT MICROENTREPREURSHIP COURSE

YTEPP

Youth Training Employment Partnership Programme

Arima

December - May

2010 CERTIFICATE OF EXCELLENCE MICROSOFT CERTIFIED APPLICATION

SPECIALIST BORDERCOM

Bordercom International Business & Technology Learning Center

2009 CERTIFICATE IN SECRETARIAL & ADMINISTRATIVE PROCEDURES

**TVC** 

Trinizuela Technical & Vocational College

**CERTIFIACTE IN TYPEWRITING-**First Class Pass

**CERTIFICATE IN OFFICE PROCEDURES-**First Class Pass

**CERTIFICATE IN ENGLISH FOR BUSINESS COMMUNICATION-First Class** 

**Pass** 

July - September

2009 CIVILIAN CONSERVATION CORPS

Successfully Completed Cycle 0902

April – September

2008 COMPLETION OF MICRSOFT WINDOWS-INTERMEDIATE LEVEL

**SBCS** 

School of Business & Computer Sciences

April - May

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2009-2012 <u>HUMAN RESOURCE DEPARTMENT-MILAT/MYPART MILITARY</u>

**ACADEMY** 

Administrative Assistant:-

> Assistant to Human Resource Manager

- Prepare Timesheets: assists in recruitment and selection process
- > Prepare reports: assist in maintenance of programme budgets
- > Faxing /Scanning and sending documents
- ➤ Effective management of staff records

2012-Present HUMAN RESOURCE DEPARTMENT -MILAT MILITARY ACADEMY

**Administrative Assistant/Supervisor** 

- ➤ Assistant to Human Resource Manager
- > Typing Memoranda's, Reports
- > Flagging Documents
- ➤ Office Etiquette
- > Telephone Duties
- Duplicating Documents

# 2006-2008 GREEN STREET SPORTS BAR AND GRILL Manager/Bartender

- > Oversaw stock taking process to ensure operational efficiency
- ➤ Maintained high level of customer service
- > Updated and balanced accounts on a daily basis
- Ensured compliance with health and safety regulation

# 2006-2007 <u>JUMBO FOODS SUPERMARKET</u>

#### Cashier

- > Implemented a high level of customer service to both internal and external customers
- Cashing of Goods
- > Training to new cashiers

### 2005-2006 <u>EASTERN AUCTION MART</u>

#### **Office Assistant**

- > Prepared letters, memo's
- Billing
- Customer Service Representative

## **REFERENCES**

#### Mr. Stephen Hodge

Human Resource Manager MiLAT Military Academy 642-2924/740-5725

Mr. Kenwrick Elie Warrant Officer Class 1

Trinidad and Tobago Defence Force Reserves

740-0612